the mumbo for mayor t-shirts are still
available for a little bit of time link
is in the description we're back on the
hermit craft server and last episode I
did quite a lot of work to the mansion
we made all of this right side and I
want this episode to do all of the left
hand side and some more but as I was
preparing to do this I found this in the
middle of my base a cartography table
and an anvil then I didn't put it there
I did not put it there and then I saw
this a white banner and I didn't put
that there either so something was
immediately up and and then I saw this a
bunch of signs on a door I don't know
why they used a door I have nothing to
do with doors it's time to grab greens
booty find all seven on the map to
receive your Lutie nice use of a rind
there and then I started looking at my
map and I didn't see much and after a
while I started to see some little
letters there greens
booty and it turns out there was more
than one there was indeed seven
locations marked out on this map and
then I thought I should probably hit
record because everyone loves a treasure
hunt so let's go out and see if we can
find them so the first one I think was
over yet that definitely looks like it
it was in this pond so what have we got
oh my good shock a box full of grave
wool who did no one put a sign saying
what this was so I think it might have
been tango purely because I was
streaming and I was filling in for scar
the other day and he told me to leave so
I mean that's that suspicious in itself
there was definitely one over by Big Ben
the giant drill yep yeah there's another
one and then there was one yep here it
is crack mumbos Kakuma keep yeah kikyo's
is a sneaky man I think it is just as
simple as you hit that yes hit the
button and then enter
the ultimate oh my goodness this is a
prize a whole shocker box of dark
prismarine wow wow wow wow wow I spent
ten minutes looking for this one is it
under ground cyan terracotta it's just
all the blocks my base is made it's like
tango knew I was gonna do an enormous
time-lapse today and the last one was on
stresses base gray concrete powder well
that actually brings us on to what we're
gonna be doing for the first part of
this video which is really important
Wow look at all these resources seven
schalke boxes full of resources because
what we're gonna be doing today is the
great mansion expansion as I've been
saying I want to build an awful lot
today and this is going to come in very
very handy so thank you so much tango
for this and I think without further ado
we should use this right now and get all
of this started let's go
[Music]
[Applause]
wow-whee this is a moment that I have
been waiting for for a really long time
look at this it's got chimneys it's got
some lighting but most of all it's got
nearly all the shape that it requires
this is pretty much it for the build in
terms of shape in terms of detail this
is it it is mostly complete and it was
it was a long sprint to the end for this
build but we are finally there is some
glass miss every time i zoom in I see
another block missing that must have
been missing from the start of this
whole project this glass been missing
and fixed but that literally must have
been there since well pretty much since
we started the project but what do we
think of this it's obviously still not
entirely complete but this semicircle
I'm gonna I'm gonna do a little bit of a
flyby so that we can get a good angle on
all of this you can really see the
Halfmoon shape kinda looks like a banana
kinda looks like a banana now you might
be wondering what these bits are for and
they overlap with each other I actually
just need to get some water to show you
these are really cool like aqueduct
waterway systems they're purely for
aesthetic purposes of course this is
that this is the lazy man's way of
building this just get you let yourself
get pushed along while you place the
water and then eventually it goes
straight into the one over here and they
overlap perfectly there we go that gives
it a little bit more color now there are
lots of things that still need to be
done on this build and it won't surprise
you that the back is not complete I'll
show you that a second but one of the
things that I really need to add to this
build is foliage there's a little bit of
grass as you can see but what
really needs some trees some proper
trees the only one that's got is right
there and it looks a little bit lonely
as it is literally the only one so I
need some gardening wait doesn't either
have a gardening service I need some
gardening
I literally need some flowers I need
some brighter colors because it does
look although very impressive maybe
lacking a little bit of color but that's
what all of the greeneries for I've been
debating with myself for quite some time
how to do the back and I'm actually
wondering if I even need to because I
literally don't come back here how many
times have you seen this apart from me
showing it never because I don't come
back here and no one else does so I
might just fix up that little hole
that's not exactly a little but I may
just leave this relatively undetailed
for now so I think as long as it's
looking pretty clean I can live with it
but I also think it's fair to say
without all of these resources that
tango gave me during that treasure hunt
I don't think I would have been able to
complete that time-lapse not at all so
now we've done a lot of building it's
time to go and visit Grum bot because if
you remember last episode we built drum
bots grumbles little brother and we need
to a scrum but what exactly exactly do
we do now why do we always start these
recordings on top of an end rod on
either side of this platform the thing
is like we both just we just stand on it
when there's no communication it's just
we both started you know and then
gradually just hop off and start looking
at this thing that is like the ritual
basically right we have we've done what
grumbo said I can see you've built up
your film studio looking good of course
and I'm up the the Graham bot shop or
the drum bot shop which is incredibly
difficult to say yeah now tell us what
to do again yes basically that seems to
be the question that we we just throw at
this thing just like what next reveal
the next plan the plan tell us what to
you say what should we do we have done
what you said we
yeah just go straight to the point yeah
we've done what you asked olan olan
one two three four okay I don't know why
I always get really nervous before this
but I'm assuming he gets angry he's just
gonna smite you Oh Oh another mrs.
grumble is proud of you that is so sweet
that is very cute grandma is proud of
you okay so but he's oh he's giving us
further instructions though brahmbhatt
will now supply the plan create us you
must sell diamonds the budget for
support on the mumbo for mayor campaign
in the shop sorry wait that's what the
budgets for we're giving them away but
selling diamonds is that that sounds
really shame that sounds really Shady
wait I think that might be the loophole
right like we're not we're no we're not
we're not young people support we're
selling diamonds for their support for
their support it it's true that is that
is different you must also use the
studio to film an advert for Mambo for
mayor okay so we have to make an advert
for Mambo firm air that sounds I guess I
mean that does make sense I mean how I
feel about selling the diamonds
for support this is a bit weird this
piece of paper that says crumble is
proud of you I kind of want another one
well things have oh he's referred he
said good luck dad's as well oh yeah so
we've gone from creators the dad's good
luck dad I mean I really I really hope
he's not becoming too sentient I mean I
don't I hope he doesn't come to us with
difficult questions and things
well again I do wonder what we've
created here yeah so do I refer to him
as son now no it's weird to grumble
will refer to miss Graham before then
occasionally son if he requests it may
be okay
I've got an idea but I wanted to make
the the the diamond thing a little less
weird cuz you know right I think you
know I think he's found a loophole in
the system but I think we could offer
some more I think what we should do
yeah for people to show their support
for mumbo firmer with every purchase of
diamond blocks that's right yeah from
every purchase of diamond blocks we give
them a free mustache to show their
support this is like part of the deal
why is it that most plans in this season
permit craft seems seem to lead to me
losing my moustache in some form or when
the steps ending up somewhere else okay
real bad okay bad enough that I'm
willing to give away my moustache and
what if also if they if they bought two
diamond blocks they could really show
their support by running our TV advert I
mean that could be really funny yeah
yeah yeah more diamond blocks for them
for more support I mean that that makes
total sense that made exactly that makes
so much sense
grumble you're a genius okay exactly
right we're gonna they're gonna have to
shave your head okay Cheers
I appreciate the fact you just have
shares in your ender chest ready to go
my ender chest is the equivalent of
someone putting their hands in their
pocket and pulling out like most random
assortment of junk okay are you ready
buddy I get it shave your head lots of
moustaches I'll be coming from my head
oh yeah let's take a look excluding the
one that was already there we got of
course yet one two three four five extra
buy more I'm sure hold on did you been
rocking a beard by the looks of things
it's a full-blown
the chin being that look that look down
as well yeah you got back all right we
got seven mustaches to give away for
support you look so good honey you look
so funny I mean I don't think I've had a
single a single week it's been too long
as she feels weird seeing me with my
usual skin it's it's bizarre goodness
sake alright let's let's go okay what do
you guys should we film the thing that
won't take long
yeah yeah let's do it let's do it you
got a whole studio in here oh yeah yeah
yeah green screen dolly track who's got
villager trader cinema camera in your
head you're always just name the camera
Brandi yeah alright okay so what you
want me to do I mean nothing in your
hand and then well I just want you to be
mumbo for me be the mare that you're
supposed to be you ready okay all right
and three two one action no okay I
thought that was just a her oh I thought
I'd do the look away from the camera you
know like a robot yet yet dude yeah well
yeah that's it that's it that's it yeah
work it work it okay do the wrong do a
jump okay you can you can fix all this
in post-production really yeah it's not
gonna look rubbish at all alright we're
gonna take all the diamonds over now to
the shop alright it might take me a
little while to take down my part of it
Graham bot junior drum bot whatever yeah
that is the cutest shop that ever lived
I am wondering though how do you where
do you go inside yes I didn't actually
install a door but here
we're just destroying our way yeah he
just
and there's also clearly no interior
whatsoever I mean you know it's at least
it's adorable from the outside it's not
what's inside that can have a face on
the inside as well it's pretty simple
right we just have a few chests and it
will have so if you just like want to
put on I know mum babe for mer t-shirt
one diamond block oh yeah yeah that's a
good move selling t-shirts selling
diamonds for if you want to if you want
a mustache it's to Diamond you can you
can it's to diamond blocks selling
chocolate makes sense and then if you
want to if you want to support Mambo
from there the most in exchange for
diamonds mm-hmm
then it is well we could put in four
then it's four for the advert there we
go I'm excited to see everyone running
the commercials and wearing the
mustaches for this later but I think you
know what I think robots both insane and
a genius yeah I think I would agree
we've created an insane genius he's
found a loophole he's found it he's
found he's broken the system exactly
well I mean hopefully it leads to me
becoming mad that's that's the end goal
and hopefully hopefully we can manage to
pull that off with grandpa's help and
the support and Hermes and and Rumble
and of course and of course jumbo he's
our grandson we're just gonna we gonna
leave that behind so we need to set up
this shop and get it up and running and
I don't even think we need an interior
all we need is graham bots face or grump
Trump drum bots face on the inside to
light all this up and of course we need
to explain how this works everywhere
stop it add in the eyes and we are done
you know he looks a lot more threatening
from the inside okay I've gone back to
my base to get everything I could
possibly need for this shop now we need
the instructions
here and then we need somewhere to put
all of these chests so the support level
one support level two and support level
three so for the cost of just one
diamond you can get yourself some
support mumbo T's that's what you got to
do if you want to support mumbo in
exchange for some diamonds you just need
to buy the diamonds and exchange you've
got to take this and put on a mambo from
there skin like me a mambo have so
that's that's one diamond for the
purchase of two diamond blocks you can
put a mambo mustache on your skin to
show your support over here you can
purchase four diamond blocks and all you
got to do is play our brand new Mambo
for mayor add now you can't take all
three and just play it three times it is
limited to one per customer so in theory
you could take this one this one and
this one and then you could have the
t-shirt the mustache and play the ad and
you would end up with seven diamond
blocks that's a stack of diamonds for
ultimate support for Mambo for mayor now
I've got to figure out how to explain
this in a book I think I've got this do
you want diamonds that's always a
brilliant way to get people to buy stuff
well we sell diamond blocks that's right
you can buy diamonds from us and the
price the price is supporting Mambo for
mayor of the shopping district sales are
limited to one purchase from each chest
per customer that might be a bit
confusing so I wrote you can purchase
from all three chests but only once any
purchase of diamond blocks and you must
support his campaign support does not
guarantee votes grumble said we had to
do that okay so we got ourselves the
book of explanation hopefully that makes
sense and we are pretty much done in
here it's looking a bit dreary in here
actually before I go so I'm gonna add
some hanging lights just to make it look
a bit more sparkly there we go that's oh
that's looking a lot cleaner i imagine
that these will go quite quickly to be
fair let's see how the hermit's take to
this in theory we could have a lot of
people running around
with the t-shirt and the mustache you're
doing a good job there drum bots
actually while we're here I don't think
it would feel right without some mumbo
for mayor posters in here
to be fair there we go that feels better
okay hopefully we get some customers
there because it looks like we need it
we're officially officially second last
oh my goodness mumbo what's been going
on false it's got loads of support
stresses got loads of support we need to
pick up the pace mumbo well we have got
an awful lot done today wouldn't you
it's been a long time since I've heard
that noise it's been a very long time
since I've heard that noise the most
annoying noise Mambo for mayor
underscore final final last commercial
done long oh my goodness I almost forgot
that this thing existed oh oh man oh man
oh man we're gonna play this we gonna
play this hold on hold on we we can't
just play it like this we got to get
ourselves comfortable
let's get ourselves that's it
comfortable mumbos done some fancy
editing get ourselves a nice TV screen
nice chair get our get our DVD player
and let's sit down and watch the watch
the commercial because this is what if
you if you purchase four diamond blocks
this is what they've got to put in their
video right you ready three two one
[Music]
[\h__\h] Bible people can't have you
saying take you stand up mumbo-jumbo
Khmer wowee
well if that doesn't get you to support
my boy from there I don't know what will
I must admit I'm not sure we actually
have a platform like I I don't want to
question grandpa but can we ask just one
question if my mo was made Maire what
would he do what'd he do that was
amazing so I'm definitely gonna play
that at the start of next episode as
well and on the topic of mumbo I did say
that every episode we were gonna go and
put in an item in his base to see if he
would notice so far so good
no no one has noticed we have put a a
brown wool up there and we put a lantern
just above there so now I think I reckon
we should put the jukebox somewhere I
think we should put this jukebox
somewhere see if he notices it right
there see if he notices anything
different but so far so good and I think
unfortunately that is all we have time
for today it has been a monumental
episode I spent days putting this
together and we have finally made the
majority of the actual build this I'm
not saying that this is finished it's
not finished but there is most of the
hard work done the mansion itself is
there it's just about decorating the
ugly parts now maybe adding some trees
etc but we are mostly there for now next
episode I hope to get the barge upgraded
again and probably do some more stock
and all sorts man it's a busy time on
the hermit craft server and I'm hoping
that the the date of the actual voting
will be announced very very soon as well
be good to know when that is so we can
start working towards
man this base is looking pretty cool the
mansion expansion and remember there are
also some mumbo firmer t-shirts link is
in the description if you want to show
your support as well so that's it for me
everyone thank you very much for
watching I hope you have enjoyed this
episode and I shall see you in the next
episode of hermit craft thanks very much
for watching and good